thanks hun Isn't it nice when everything
goes according to
plan everything fits your clothes your
schedule this one but every now and then
life throws you a curveball and someone
gets sick nice try if you're
self-employed like us don't have
coverage at work or are retiring soon
you need to be prepared here thanks to
flex care from manual life we're ready
for expenses not covered by our
government health insurance plan Flex
care offers coverage for prescription
drugs Dental Care and Vision Care Plus
other unexpected expenses like
chiropractors physiotherapist and more
and there's no medical questionnaire
required for many Flex care plans all
this with an easy access Flex care
card don't wait plan ahead call 1866 618
422 right now and get Flex care today
call 1866 618 422 for a free brochure or
visit coverme.com and apply online today
flexcare from Manu life